[{"Date": "2020-07-24 05:48:55+00:00", "question": "[21/21] The colour of water of which lake turned pink due to a large presence of the salt-loving Haloarchaea microbes?", "option1": "Dal lake", "option2": "Chilika lake", "option3": "Lonar lake", "option4": "Wular lake", "option5": "Loktak lake", "Answer": "Lonar lake"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:48:23+00:00", "question": "[20/21] National Mango Day was observed on which date?", "option1": "22 July", "option2": "20 July", "option3": "24  july", "option4": "21 July", "option5": "23 July", "Answer": "22 July"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:47:51+00:00", "question": "[19/21] India successfully test-fires \u201cDhruvastra\u201d anti-guided missiles. What is the Maximum Range of these Missiles?", "option1": "25km", "option2": "15km", "option3": "10km", "option4": "5km", "option5": "7km", "Answer": "7km"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:47:20+00:00", "question": "[18/21] Govt has extended Work from Home for IT, BPO companies till which date due to COVID-19?", "option1": "31 July 2020", "option2": "30 November 2020", "option3": "31 December 2020", "option4": "31 October 2020", "option5": "31 January 2021", "Answer": "31 December 2020"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:46:48+00:00", "question": "[17/21] Which bank has launched\u00a0\u2018Insta Click Savings Account\u2019?", "option1": "SBI", "option2": "ICICI", "option3": "Bank of Baroda", "option4": "Kotak Mahindra Bank", "option5": "Union Bank of India", "Answer": "Bank of Baroda"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:46:16+00:00", "question": "[16/21] Who has been appointed as MD & CEO of SBI General Insurance?", "option1": "Sanjay Agarwal", "option2": "V Vaidyanath", "option3": "Shyam srinivasan", "option4": "Rakesh sharma", "option5": "P C Kandpal", "Answer": "P C Kandpal"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:45:44+00:00", "question": "[15/21] Who among the following won the inaugural Gulbenkian Prize for Humanity? \nA. Malena Ernman  B. Greta Thunberg \nC. Naomi Seibt  D. Boris Johnson  E. Angela Merkel ", "option1": "C", "option2": "A", "option3": "D", "option4": "B", "option5": "E", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:45:12+00:00", "question": "[14/21] Which state has signed an MoU with AMUL to help Women Self Help Groups and to Boost Milk Cooperatives? \nA. Telangana  B. Andhra Pradesh \nC. Karnataka  D. Tamilnadu  E. Madhya Pradesh", "option1": "B", "option2": "E", "option3": "C", "option4": "A", "option5": "D", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:44:40+00:00", "question": "[13/21] Punjab government signed MoU with which IIT for skill development? \nA) IIT Delhi  B) IIT Madras \nC) IIT Kharagpur  D) IIT Mandi  E) IIT Ropar ", "option1": "B", "option2": "D", "option3": "C", "option4": "E", "option5": "A", "Answer": "E"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:44:08+00:00", "question": "[12/21] The National Payment Corporation of India (NPCI) launched which UPI Feature for recurring payments? ", "option1": "UPI direct Pay", "option2": "UPI Auto Pay", "option3": "UPI Card Pay", "option4": "UPI Schedule Pay", "option5": "UPI EMI Pay", "Answer": "UPI Auto Pay"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:43:36+00:00", "question": "[11/21] Who has appointed as Chairman of the Technical Advisory Committee of NFRA?", "option1": "R Narayanaswamy", "option2": "Satish Reddy", "option3": "Shantanu Preetam", "option4": "R K Narayanan", "option5": "B. Ramesh Bidhuri", "Answer": "R Narayanaswamy"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:43:04+00:00", "question": "[10/21] Who among the following has been appointed as the CMD of National Mineral Development Corporation? \nA) Rakesh Verma B) Sumit Deb \nC) Pravin Kumar D) Rajat Singh  E) Anand Gupta", "option1": "B", "option2": "C", "option3": "A", "option4": "D", "option5": "E", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:42:33+00:00", "question": "[9/21] HIL (India) has supplied 20.60 MT of DDT to which country for Malaria control program?", "option1": "Oman", "option2": "Kenya", "option3": "Uganda", "option4": "Brazil", "option5": "South Africa", "Answer": "South Africa"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:42:01+00:00", "question": "[8/21] E-Sachivalaya portal is launched by which state? \nA) Madhya Pradesh  B) Haryana \nC) Uttar Pradesh  D) Chhattisgarh  E) Odisha", "option1": "E", "option2": "B", "option3": "C", "option4": "A", "option5": "D", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:41:29+00:00", "question": "[7/21] According to New design of Ayodhya's grand Ram temple, What will be the Height  of the Temple? \nA. 151 Feet  B. 161 Feet  C. 172 Feet\nD. 176 Feet E. 171 Feet", "option1": "D", "option2": "E", "option3": "A", "option4": "C", "option5": "B", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:40:57+00:00", "question": "[6/21] Name the drone, which the Defence Research and Development Org (DRDO) has provided to the Indian Army for accurate surveillance? \nA. India   B. Bharat  C. Third Eye \nD. Small Spy  E. Hidden eye", "option1": "C", "option2": "E", "option3": "D", "option4": "B", "option5": "A", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:40:25+00:00", "question": "[5/21] Recently, PM Modi interacted with Arvind Krishna. Arvind Krishna is currently serving as the CEO of _______. \nA. Walmart  B. IBM  C. Oracle \nD. Accenture  E. Phillips", "option1": "D", "option2": "C", "option3": "E", "option4": "A", "option5": "B", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:39:54+00:00", "question": "[4/21] Which public sector bank has signed corporate agency pact with Life Insurance Corporation of India?", "option1": "State Bank of India", "option2": "Bank of India", "option3": "UCO Bank", "option4": "Union Bank of India", "option5": "Bank of Baroda", "Answer": "Union Bank of India"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:39:22+00:00", "question": "[3/21] Which actor has launched a free online platform called, \"Pravasi Rojgar\" in Maharashtra?", "option1": "Aamir Khan", "option2": "Milind Soman", "option3": "Akshay Kumar", "option4": "Vicky Kaushal", "option5": "Sonu Sood", "Answer": "Sonu Sood"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:38:50+00:00", "question": "[2/21] The president of which country initiated the proposal to United Nations to declare 2021 as International Year of Peace and Trust? ", "option1": "India", "option2": "Thailand", "option3": "Philippines", "option4": "Malaysia", "option5": "Turkmenistan", "Answer": "Turkmenistan"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:38:15+00:00", "question": "[1/21] Which country conducted a successful flight test of the MGTD-20 gas turbine engine made by 3D-printing for the 1st time ? \nA) Israel B) China  C) USA D) India \nE)  Russia", "option1": "E", "option2": "B", "option3": "A", "option4": "C", "option5": "D", "Answer": "E"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 05:29:56+00:00", "question": "Ready Guys?", "option1": "Yes", "option2": "No", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:55:50+00:00", "question": "[26/26] Rajya Sabha secretariat has launched the employee\u2019s welfare scheme on the name of whom?", "option1": "Sushma Swaraj", "option2": "Jyoti Basu", "option3": "Atal Bihari Vajpayee", "option4": "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel", "option5": "Arun Jaitley", "Answer": "Arun Jaitley"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:55:18+00:00", "question": "[25/26] Recently In which state Rare yellow turtle discovered in India?", "option1": "Tripura", "option2": "Aasam", "option3": "Sikkim", "option4": "Odisha", "option5": "Mizoram", "Answer": "Odisha"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:54:46+00:00", "question": "[24/26] Who heads the Investment Clearance Cell (ICC) set up by Ministry of civil aviation for assistance Land clearance of proposals in domestic civil aviation industry ?", "option1": "Sateesh Reddy", "option2": "Sanjeevanee Kutty", "option3": "Gargi Kaul", "option4": "Rajiv Gauba", "option5": "Amber Dubey", "Answer": "Amber Dubey"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:54:14+00:00", "question": "[23/26] MG Motor India Pvt Ltd has signed a MoU with which organisation to set up fast chargers for electric vehicles? \nA. EESL  B. BEL  C. Tata Power Ltd \nD. Torrent Power  E. NTPC", "option1": "A", "option2": "D", "option3": "B", "option4": "E", "option5": "C", "Answer": "C"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:53:43+00:00", "question": "[22/26] Which State's Cabinet has approved \"One-Stop-Shop\" Scheme-OSS to fast track investment and capacity expansion proposals by facilitating time-bound approvals and clearances? ", "option1": "Gujarat", "option2": "Rajasthan", "option3": "Uttar Pradesh", "option4": "Odisha", "option5": "Madhya Pradesh", "Answer": "Rajasthan"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:53:11+00:00", "question": "[21/26] The Indian Navy conducted the PASSEX with the United States  Navy. Which nuclear-powered aircraft carrier was used by the US Navy in exercise? ", "option1": "USS Ardent", "option2": "USS Rechard", "option3": "USS Nimitz", "option4": "USS George", "option5": "USS Virginia", "Answer": "USS Nimitz"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:52:39+00:00", "question": "[20/26] Environment ministry has cleared approval of the Zonal Master Plan of which eco sensitive zone ?", "option1": "Barnawapara Eco-Sensitive Zone", "option2": "Bhindawas Eco-Sensitive Zone", "option3": "Sultanpur Eco-Sensitive Zone", "option4": "Bhagirathi Eco-Sensitive Zone", "option5": "Netravali Eco-Sensitive Zone", "Answer": "Bhagirathi Eco-Sensitive Zone"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:52:07+00:00", "question": "[19/26] The Consumer Protection Act (CPA), 2019 has come into effect from which date?", "option1": "August 31, 2020", "option2": "July 22, 2020", "option3": "August 1, 2020", "option4": "July 21, 2020", "option5": "July 20, 2020", "Answer": "July 20, 2020"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:51:35+00:00", "question": "[18/26] Which of the following has provided drones named \u2018Bharat\u2019 to the Indian Army?", "option1": "CSIR", "option2": "IISc Banglore", "option3": "BHEL", "option4": "ISRO", "option5": "DRDO", "Answer": "DRDO"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:51:04+00:00", "question": "[17/26] India will strengthen its marine  \ncapabilities by inducting four more  \nP-8I multi-mission aircraft from which country?  A.Russia  B.France C.Israel  D.USA E.Japan", "option1": "B", "option2": "D", "option3": "A", "option4": "E", "option5": "C", "Answer": "D"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:50:32+00:00", "question": "[16/26] Which state\u2019s cabinet gave approval to \u2018Samadhan se Vikas\u2019, a one-time settlement scheme for the recovery of long-pending dues? \nA) Gujarat  B) Rajasthan  C) Haryana \nD) Odisha  E) Chhattisgarh ", "option1": "B", "option2": "D", "option3": "C", "option4": "E", "option5": "A", "Answer": "C"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:50:00+00:00", "question": "[15/26] Which country proposed the United Nations to dedicate the year 2020 as International Year of Plant Health?", "option1": "Finland", "option2": "New Zealand", "option3": "Sweden", "option4": "Russia", "option5": "USA", "Answer": "Finland"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:49:28+00:00", "question": "[14/26] India with which country signed an agreement to establish \u201cEmergency Medical Services?", "option1": "Indonesia", "option2": "Nepal", "option3": "Bhutan", "option4": "Bangladesh", "option5": "Maldives", "Answer": "Maldives"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:48:57+00:00", "question": "[13/26] South Korea launched its first military communications satellite, Army/Navy/Air Force Satellite Information System 2(ANASIS-II). Who has developed it? ", "option1": "NASA", "option2": "CNSA", "option3": "Virgin Galactic", "option4": "SpaceX", "option5": "Astra", "Answer": "SpaceX"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:48:25+00:00", "question": "[12/26] The Total no. of seats is likely to increase in the Parliament by which year?  \nA. 2021 B. 2026  C. 2022  D. 2024  \nE. 2025", "option1": "D", "option2": "E", "option3": "A", "option4": "C", "option5": "B", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:47:53+00:00", "question": "[11/26] Who has been appointed as the Director, Serious Fraud Investigation Office (SFIO)?  \nA. Rajiv Kumar  B. Satish Reddy \nC. Manoj Ahuja  D. Keshav Chandra   E. Varsha Joshi", "option1": "A", "option2": "B", "option3": "D", "option4": "E", "option5": "C", "Answer": "D"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:47:21+00:00", "question": "[10/26] BCCI will seek the government's permission to stage 2020's Indian Premier League (IPL) in which country?", "option1": "Saudi Arabia", "option2": "Australia", "option3": "Bangladesh", "option4": "UAE", "option5": "South Africa", "Answer": "UAE"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:46:49+00:00", "question": "[9/26] Who has been appointed as the President and Managing Director for SAP Indian Subcontinent?", "option1": "Ekjot Arora", "option2": "Chetanjeet Ahuja", "option3": "Dhanmeet Taneja", "option4": "Guneet Singh", "option5": "Kulmeet Bawa", "Answer": "Kulmeet Bawa"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:46:18+00:00", "question": "[8/26] who has been appointed as the MD&CEO of Karur Vysya Bank? \nA) Arun Singhal  B) PVS Suryakumar \nC) Shaji KV  D) P R Seshadri  E) Ramesh Babu", "option1": "A", "option2": "B", "option3": "C", "option4": "E", "option5": "D", "Answer": "E"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:45:46+00:00", "question": "[7/26] According to a report by the World  \nFederation of Direct Selling Associations (WFDSA), India has been ranked _______ on direct selling industry Index. \nA. 11  B. 15  C. 21  D. 17  E. 27", "option1": "A", "option2": "E", "option3": "C", "option4": "D", "option5": "B", "Answer": "B"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:45:14+00:00", "question": "[6/26] Which IIM institution has come up with a unique user-friendly wearable device named \u201cVeli Band\u201d?", "option1": "IIM Kolkata", "option2": "IIM Ahmedabad", "option3": "IIM Bangalore", "option4": "IIM Kozikhode", "option5": "IIM Indore", "Answer": "IIM Kozikhode"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:44:42+00:00", "question": "[5/26] Which Payment App has announced the launch of India\u2019s first numberless card ?  \nA.FreeCharge  B.Paytm  C.PhonePe \nD.FamPay  E.JioPay", "option1": "C", "option2": "B", "option3": "A", "option4": "D", "option5": "E", "Answer": "D"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:44:11+00:00", "question": "[4/26] Union Minister of Health and Family Welfare, Harsh Vardhan launched the CSR campaign to prevent spread of COVID-19 of which public sector bank recently?", "option1": "UCO Bank", "option2": "Punjab National Bank", "option3": "Bank of Maharashtra", "option4": "State Bank of India", "option5": "Indian Overseas Bank", "Answer": "Punjab National Bank"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:43:39+00:00", "question": "[3/26] Which state government has announced to launch an anti- dengue campaign? \nA. Madhya Pradesh  B. Uttar Pradesh \nC. Uttarakhand  D. Himachal Pradesh E. Odisha", "option1": "C", "option2": "B", "option3": "E", "option4": "A", "option5": "D", "Answer": "C"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:43:07+00:00", "question": "[2/26] Juan Marse passed away recently was renowned __________?", "option1": "Actor", "option2": "Footballer", "option3": "Photographer", "option4": "Nobelist", "option5": "Scientist", "Answer": "Nobelist"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:42:35+00:00", "question": "[1/26] Which state/ UT has approved the \"Mukhyamantri Ghar Ghar Ration Yojana\"? \nA. Delhi  B. Chhattisgarh  C. Goa \nD. Uttar Pradesh  E. Madhya Pradesh", "option1": "D", "option2": "C", "option3": "E", "option4": "B", "option5": "A", "Answer": "A"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:38:11+00:00", "question": "[10/26] Which country proposed the United Nations to dedicate the year 2020 as International Year of Plant Health?", "option1": "New Zealand", "option2": "Russia", "option3": "Sweden", "option4": "Finland", "option5": "USA", "Answer": "Finland"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:37:39+00:00", "question": "[9/26] Which State's Cabinet has approved \"One-Stop-Shop\" Scheme-OSS to fast track investment and capacity expansion proposals by facilitating time-bound approvals and clearances? ", "option1": "Rajasthan", "option2": "Gujarat", "option3": "Odisha", "option4": "Madhya Pradesh", "option5": "Uttar Pradesh", "Answer": "Rajasthan"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:37:07+00:00", "question": "[8/26] Rajya Sabha secretariat has launched the employee\u2019s welfare scheme on the name of whom?", "option1": "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel", "option2": "Arun Jaitley", "option3": "Atal Bihari Vajpayee", "option4": "Jyoti Basu", "option5": "Sushma Swaraj", "Answer": "Arun Jaitley"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:36:35+00:00", "question": "[7/26] The Indian Navy conducted the PASSEX with the United States  Navy. Which nuclear-powered aircraft carrier was used by the US Navy in exercise? ", "option1": "USS Nimitz", "option2": "USS Rechard", "option3": "USS George", "option4": "USS Virginia", "option5": "USS Ardent", "Answer": "USS Nimitz"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:36:03+00:00", "question": "[6/26] MG Motor India Pvt Ltd has signed a MoU with which organisation to set up fast chargers for electric vehicles? \nA. EESL  B. BEL  C. Tata Power Ltd \nD. Torrent Power  E. NTPC", "option1": "C", "option2": "B", "option3": "E", "option4": "A", "option5": "D", "Answer": "C"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:35:32+00:00", "question": "[5/26] BCCI will seek the government's permission to stage 2020's Indian Premier League (IPL) in which country?", "option1": "South Africa", "option2": "Saudi Arabia", "option3": "Bangladesh", "option4": "UAE", "option5": "Australia", "Answer": "UAE"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:35:00+00:00", "question": "[4/26] Recently In which state Rare yellow turtle discovered in India?", "option1": "Tripura", "option2": "Sikkim", "option3": "Mizoram", "option4": "Odisha", "option5": "Aasam", "Answer": "Odisha"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:34:28+00:00", "question": "[3/26] Which of the following has provided drones named \u2018Bharat\u2019 to the Indian Army?", "option1": "CSIR", "option2": "ISRO", "option3": "IISc Banglore", "option4": "DRDO", "option5": "BHEL", "Answer": "DRDO"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:33:56+00:00", "question": "[2/26] Which state government has announced to launch an anti- dengue campaign? \nA. Madhya Pradesh  B. Uttar Pradesh \nC. Uttarakhand  D. Himachal Pradesh E. Odisha", "option1": "D", "option2": "B", "option3": "E", "option4": "C", "option5": "A", "Answer": "C"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:33:24+00:00", "question": "[1/26] Who heads the Investment Clearance Cell (ICC) set up by Ministry of civil aviation for assistance Land clearance of proposals in domestic civil aviation industry ?", "option1": "Rajiv Gauba", "option2": "Sanjeevanee Kutty", "option3": "Amber Dubey", "option4": "Gargi Kaul", "option5": "Sateesh Reddy", "Answer": "Amber Dubey"}, {"Date": "2020-07-23 05:29:56+00:00", "question": "Ready Guys?", "option1": "Yes", "option2": "No", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"This quiz channel use quiz bot :-": 66}]